<?xml version="1.0"?>
  <channel>
    <title>Astrology.com Monthly Overview</title>
    <link>http://www.astrology.com/us/offsite/rss/monthly-overview.aspx</link>
    <description>Get free Horoscopes and Astrology from Astrology.com.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>http://www.astrology.com/img/logo-300x40.png</url>
      <title>Astrology.com feed of Monthly Overview</title>
      <link>http://www.astrology.com/us/offsite/rss/monthly-overview.aspx</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Aries Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of clarity and transformative connection, Aries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;October 6 cracks open a season of truth-seeking as Mercury enters Scorpio and stirs your eighth house of intimacy, inheritance, and emotional entanglements. You&#39;re listening and decoding. Private conversations and raw reflections push you closer to what you truly need.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, the Aries full moon ignites your first house of self to spotlight autonomy and the image you&#39;ve outgrown. A version of you that once helped you cope no longer matches your vibe. Shed it and reclaim the person you came here to be.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the thirteenth, Venus enters Libra and lights a match in your seventh house of chemistry, connection, and partnerships. Reciprocity becomes magnetic. Who you attract now mirrors your clarity and cravings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later in the day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius, recharging your eleventh house of future visions. Your friendships mature as you see exactly who&#39;s aligned and who&#39;s expired.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 is the start of a new story in love, business, or both! Agreements shift while something beautiful asks for your signature.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neptune retrogrades into Pisces on the twenty-second and slips into your twelfth house. Rest becomes a source of restoration and revelation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, the sun enters Scorpio, tuning your emotions to what trust feels like.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on October 29 and activates your ninth house of adventure. It&#39;s time to move, publish, show up, or study. Your beliefs are evolving, and what you believe becomes what you build.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Aries!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 6, 14, 26&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 3, 12, 28</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=aries</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taurus Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of relational refinement and magnetism, Taurus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Scorpio on October 6, directing focus to your seventh house of partnerships, reflection, and interpersonal truth. This is an invitation to ask better questions in love and business. Communication turns intimate while conversations become catalysts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the same day, the Aries full moon activates your twelfth house of solitude and healing. Let endings rise as you shed outdated expectations, especially those you&#39;ve internalized about what you owe others. There&#39;s peace in acknowledging what&#39;s over.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venus enters Libra on the thirteenth and restores harmony to your sixth house of health, rituals, and alignment. Soft structure becomes alluring.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The same day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius, reawakening your tenth house of career, reputation, and ambition. You&#39;re evolving how you lead. Power feels less like control and more like clarity. Watch what themes surface around visibility or long-term vision!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 helps you rebalance your daily life with love, care, and beauty. Use this lunar portal to commit to habits that honor the future you&#39;re building.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On October 22, Neptune retrogrades into Pisces and slips into your eleventh house of friendship and future dreams. Something synchronistic may arrive. That same day, the sun enters Scorpio and reciprocity gets real. Let partnerships reflect what you&#39;re finally ready for.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on the twenty-ninth, activating your eighth house of energetic exchanges and psychological depth. Use words to open portals, not close doors. Your mindset around trust, pleasure, and shared power is transforming.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Taurus!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 8, 17, 27&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 2, 15, 29</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=taurus</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of creative revival and alignment, Gemini.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On October 6, Mercury enters Scorpio and awakens your sixth house of ritual, work/life rhythm, and well-being. Planning becomes sacred. Don&#39;t underestimate the momentum found in routines! You&#39;re rethinking your schedule not to do more but to live better.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That same day, the Aries full moon lights up your eleventh house of community and long-term visions. A shared dream will either reach a conclusion or emerge for correction. Release alliances that no longer reflect your purpose.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Venus enters Libra on the thirteenth, your fifth house of passion, artistry, and magnetism glows with energy. Romance becomes a canvas, and your signature charisma is the paint. Pleasure is a necessity for your nervous system, so let yourself be adored!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later the same day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius, reigniting your ninth house of belief, expansion, and adventure. A long-held vision may stir again while your higher calling asks for structure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 invites you to reset your joy. Initiate art and choose love not as distraction but as devotion. There&#39;s extra power in your play.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the twenty-second, Neptune retrogrades into Pisces and your tenth house of legacy. What do you need to feel empowered? Adjust the dream. That same day, the sun enters Scorpio to awaken your deeper purpose.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on October 29 and shifts the focus to your seventh house of love, commitment, and partnership. Speak with both courage and care as you honor evolving contracts and connections.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Gemini!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 10, 14, 30&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 5, 11, 29</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=gemini</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of emotional renovation and creative evolution, Cancer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Mercury enters Scorpio on October 6, your fifth house of joy, romance, and expression asks you to stop censoring yourself. What once felt indulgent now feels essential.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, the Aries full moon peaks in your tenth house of career and long-term goals. You&#39;re shedding an old role and with it the pressure to perform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the thirteenth, Venus enters Libra and infuses your fourth house of home, lineage, and emotions with softness. Make space for beauty! Nourish your environment until it soothes your nervous system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours later, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius and reawakens your eighth house of trust and transformation. What&#39;s been buried begins to bloom once more. An old fear loses its grip and your power starts to move again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 offers a genuine reset for your living situation, family, and inner world. Share your energy with the people and places that feel safe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the twenty-second, Neptune retrogrades into Pisces, activating your ninth house of philosophy and adventure. Let old, rigid beliefs dissolve.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That evening, the sun enters Scorpio and invites you into realignment, risk, and artistic resurgence. Pleasure is the solution for a lack mindset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on October 29, bringing focus to your sixth house of rituals, health, and daily habits. Focus on practical improvements that honor your rhythm. Let your routines reflect your passion. You&#39;re not here to play small at work or perform politeness anymore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Cancer!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 8, 25, 28&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 1, 17, 20</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=cancer</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leo Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of heart-led love and luminous expansion, Leo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Scorpio on October 6 and activates your fourth house of home, family, and emotional roots. Every conversation carries a deeper undertone and every silence holds a hidden message.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Aries full moon the same day illuminates your ninth house of expansion and adventure, revealing future plans. Travel or spiritual growth takes on urgency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the thirteenth, Venus enters Libra and softens your third house of communication and connection. Whether reconnecting, negotiating with charm, or repackaging a project, it&#39;s time to infuse grace into your message and let beauty lead.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later that day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius and your seventh house of committed relationships. What once simmered beneath the surface suddenly demands clarity. Say yes to something serious and walk away from anything too small.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 awakens cognition and creative articulation. This lunation resets your relationship with spoken, written, and intuitive language. Give yourself space to flirt, post, and pitch!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sun enters Scorpio on the twenty-second, and your emotions require self-loyalty. This is a chance to reconnect with the version of you that doesn&#39;t need an audience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, Neptune retrogrades into Pisces to amplify your eighth house of intimacy, trust, and resources. Insight emerges through inspiration while unspoken agreements, financial entanglements, or emotional debts reveal themselves.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters gregarious Sagittarius on October 29 and lights up your fifth house of romance, visibility, and risk. Your magnetism returns with a new, exciting edge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Leo!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 6, 14, 25&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 7, 12, 21</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=leo</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgo Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of sharpened instincts and unapologetic standards, Virgo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;October 6 opens the floodgates when Mercury (your ruling planet) enters Scorpio and activates your third house of perception, speech, and strategy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That same day, the Aries full moon electrifies your eighth house of intimacy and shared energy. The way you merge with others (financially and emotionally) demands a reset. Don&#39;t underestimate the cost of letting someone inside your inner sanctum.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venus enters Libra on the thirteenth and refines your second house of money and self-esteem. This is an invitation to earn with ease and protect the internal systems that build external abundance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later that day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius, stirring your sixth house of health and habits. What was once buried under burnout or fear now asks to be rebuilt with discernment. Your routines expose your relationship to personal power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 brings the beginning of a new value system. A beautiful upgrade is on the table, and it starts with what you believe you deserve.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the twenty-second, the sun enters Scorpio and brings emotional strength to your language, learning, and mental connections.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the same day, Neptune retrogrades into Pisces and reactivates your seventh house of love. Relationships from the past may boldly reappear. Stay grounded and curious.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on October 29 to bring focus to your fourth house of memory, lineage, and environment. A private secret could be shared or revealed. Sometimes the deepest revelations come through heartfelt conversations that change everything.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Virgo!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 9, 13, 28&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 4, 18, 26</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=virgo</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libra Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of allure and full-circle clarity, Libra.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Scorpio on October 6, sharpening your focus on legacy, self-leadership, and how your energy is shared. Expect conversations about money, but don&#39;t limit this to just financial currency. Acknowledge the cost of your presence and the return on your generosity! You&#39;re not meant to match the stories of your past.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also on that day, the Aries full moon lights up your seventh house of love and partnership. A cycle that began six months ago closes. Your needs evolve. You&#39;ll notice who has met you at your level and who hasn&#39;t. Don&#39;t be afraid to state the terms of your peace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the thirteenth, Venus enters Libra and softens your first house of identity, magnetism, and appearance. This is your planetary blessing of attraction! Indulge in adornment and flirtation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius and drills into your fifth house of art and self-expression. Pleasure returns with power behind it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 brings a full-body reset. Self-initiation becomes sacred as you focus less on apologizing and more on embodiment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Neptune retrogrades into Pisces on the twenty-second, your sixth house of work, health, and daily routines invites surrender where rigidity once ruled. Release the illusion of control. Later that day, the sun enters Scorpio and deepens your relationship to self-worth and material success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on October 29 and electrifies your third house of ideas and presence. Say it beautifully, boldly, and without fear.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Libra!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 2, 13, 21&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 1, 17, 30</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=libra</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorpio Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of self-reclamation and inner fire, Scorpio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The month begins with Mercury entering your sign on October 6, electrifying your inner dialogue. You&#39;re no longer biting back what needs to be said, and you&#39;re saying it with strategy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Aries full moon activating your sixth house of self-care that same day, your body becomes a messenger. Burnout, boundaries, and unspoken resentment rise to the surface. Pay attention to what aches. Energy mismanagement is no longer sustainable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thirteenth marks the entrance of Venus into Libra and your twelfth house of rest, healing, and spiritual closure. There&#39;s beauty in solitude and sweetness in what remains secret. Give yourself extra room to feel!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That same day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius, reactivating your fourth house of family, safety, and emotional patterns. You&#39;re ready to face what used to unravel you and make a different choice this time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 starts a new chapter in your inner world. Endings carry sacred momentum when you honor their purpose. Reconnect with your soul, privately and with full permission.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The twenty-second welcomes Neptune retrograde into Pisces and your fifth house of pleasure and expression. Romantic illusions might fall away, but creative clarity will emerge instead. Reclaim joy on your own terms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, the sun enters Scorpio and initiates your solar season. You&#39;re radiating magic, magnetism, and inspirational rebirth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on October 29, activating your second house of values and income. You&#39;ll feel more grounded in your voice, price, and personal power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Scorpio!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 6, 18, 25&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 2, 8, 24</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=scorpio</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sagittarius Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of intuitive alignment and unexpected sparks, Sagittarius.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Scorpio on October 6, energizing your twelfth house of rest and mystery. You&#39;re being pulled inward for meaningful, spiritual reflection.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, the Aries full moon lights up your fifth house of expression, romance, and artistic risk. Let a secret vision come to life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the thirteenth, Venus enters Libra and your eleventh house of social vibes and future dreams. Connections get warmer, more welcoming, and magnetic. This is the beginning of a new dynamic in your friendships that prioritizes mutual generosity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That same day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius and activates your third house of thought and communication. Watch what changes once exposed to the truth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21, invites you to plant exciting seeds with collaborators who see your potential clearly. Choose wisely and remember dreams need the right support system to become real.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neptune retrogrades back into Pisces on the twenty-second, softening the edges of your fourth house of home, emotions, and ancestral patterns.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sun begins its Scorpio journey the same day, deepening your awareness of what&#39;s ending and what&#39;s still sacred. Your soul asks for gentle boundaries and intentional solitude.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters your sign on October 29, and what you speak becomes a spell. Let this moment represent the return of your self-authorship. You&#39;ve spent the month dissolving attachments, observing from behind the veil. Now the veil lifts and your message matters more than ever. Realness is better than being right.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Sagittarius!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 6, 23, 29&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 5, 11, 26</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=sagittarius</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capricorn Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of recalibration, closure, and long-game clarity, Capricorn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your priorities reorient when Mercury enters Scorpio and your eleventh house of friendship and future visions on October 6. Who belongs in your orbit and who&#39;s only around for the clout?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, the Aries full moon illuminates your fourth house of home and emotional security. You might suddenly crave solitude or realize it&#39;s time to move out of a chapter you&#39;ve outgrown. Closure may not come through words but through what you choose not to repeat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venus enters Libra on the thirteenth, gracing your tenth house of legacy and reputation. Your authority becomes magnetic while soft power wins.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That same day, Pluto stations direct in Aquarius, stirring movement in your second house of earned income, resources, and values. You&#39;re rebuilding your financial foundation from the inside out with deeper self-trust. Keep all receipts!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On October 21, the Libra new moon brings a fresh start that feels less about optics and more about alignment. Take one intentional step in the direction of your future self. You&#39;re the architect now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Neptune retrogrades into Pisces on the twenty-second, you begin dissolving old mental scripts in your third house of language, thought, and communication. Misconceptions fade.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, the sun enters Scorpio to heat up your social life. Plug back into the people who actually inspire you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on October 29, activating your twelfth house of rest, reflection, and subconscious integration. You may not be saying much because silence is your sanctuary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Capricorn!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 8, 9, 26&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 1, 17, 28</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=capricorn</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquarius Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of expanded horizons and power moves, Aquarius.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mercury enters Scorpio on October 6, your tenth house of ambition, visibility, and legacy becomes a site for transformation. You&#39;re articulating long-term value over short-term wins. Your words become currency in professional spaces and can redirect the entire narrative. Choose clarity over cleverness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later that day, the Aries full moon lights up your third house of learning and local connections. If your thought patterns have changed, your outer communication will too.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venus enters Libra on the thirteenth, waking up your ninth house of adventure and perspectives. Pleasure becomes a portal to wisdom. Whether you&#39;re traveling, publishing, or exploring a new framework for love, you&#39;re drawn toward what opens your heart and mind simultaneously. This is flirtation with purpose.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pluto stations direct in Aquarius that same day, reactivating your identity and personal magnetism. The power you tried to downplay is no longer interested in hiding. What you&#39;ve metabolized since May has deepened.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On October 21, the Libra new moon offers a blank page, so write something beautiful! Let your curiosity carry you beyond the limits of your past.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the twenty-second, Neptune retrograde reenters Pisces and your second house of values and legacy building. Respect becomes emotional, embodied, and earned.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that same day, the sun enters Scorpio and intensifies your path. It&#39;s time to match your ambition with spiritual integrity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius and your eleventh house of future plans and friendship on October 29. Collaboration leads to momentum, so let people find you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Aquarius!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 2, 10, 19&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 7, 9, 24</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=aquarius</link>	
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pisces Monthly Overview for October 01, 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 -07:00</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a month of revelation, renewal, and embodiment, Pisces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On October 6, Mercury enters Scorpio and your ninth house of adventure, wisdom, and perspectives. Your worldview is being rewritten through intimacy. What you learn has the power to reorient your path completely. This is a beautiful time for writing, publishing, or planning purposeful travel that restores your sense of vision.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later that evening, the Aries full moon activates your second house of self-authority and tangible security. This lunation asks you to reflect on how you&#39;ve embodied value over the last six months. How has your relationship with money mirrored your relationship with self-respect? Let your boundaries show.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the thirteenth, Venus enters Libra and your eighth house of transformation and energetic entanglements. Pleasure becomes a portal to manifestation. Whether you&#39;re merging finances, exploring intimacy, or deepening a personal relationship, the Universe invites reciprocity. Don&#39;t settle for surface-level sweetness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pluto stations direct in Aquarius that same day, reawakening your twelfth house of shadow, healing, and surrender. What you&#39;ve been working through behind the scenes is no longer content to remain hidden.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Libra new moon on October 21 starts a new era and renewal of your soul contracts. Release energetic agreements that drain you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the twenty-second, Neptune retrograde returns to Pisces, restoring your intuitive compass. That same day, the sun enters Scorpio and illuminates your new path.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury enters Sagittarius on October 29, electrifying your tenth house of career and legacy. Don&#39;t just take up space. Decide what you want to be known for.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good luck this month, Pisces!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standout days: 18, 22, 31&lt;br&gt;Challenging days: 3, 11, 26</description>
      <link>www.astrology.com/us/horoscope/monthly-overview.aspx?sign=pisces</link>	
    </item>
  </channel>
